<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/shoko/</link><description>Recent content on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 18:09:21 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/shoko/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shoko 2021 Project Update</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-2021-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 18:09:21 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-2021-roadmap/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret our team is working on multiple projects under the Shoko umbrella. Some of them we&amp;rsquo;ve talked about publicly, either on this website, on Discord, and on other platforms, and some we&amp;rsquo;ve only discussed internall amongst the team. So with it being a new year, we thought it would be best to outline the current status on all of our projects, as well as talk about some new ones in development.</description></item><item><title>Meet Ashen, Our New Hashing Service</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/meet-ashen/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 17:24:19 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/meet-ashen/</guid><description>For a while now, one of the main concerns of the Shoko team is our current reliance on select metadata providers to the point where if a crucial metadata provider like AniDB or TvDB were to cut off access, Shoko itself would lose critical functions. To remedy this situation, we&amp;rsquo;ve been looking into alternative metadata sources and are happy to announce our partnership with animeshon, an upcoming anime &amp;amp; manga metadata provider and their perceptual hashing service Ashen.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Website Updated</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-website-updated/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 01:12:14 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-website-updated/</guid><description>While in the works for a few months now, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to launch the latest version of the Shoko Website bringing a refreshed look and a few new additions. As usual, our Discord users have gotten glimpses into the new site as it&amp;rsquo;s progressed through different iterations to finally become what you&amp;rsquo;re currently looking at.
Lets go over a few of the changes and provide some insight on what the next couple of months have in store for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Whats Next for Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/whats-next-for-shoko/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/whats-next-for-shoko/</guid><description>As mentioned earlier this week, we wanted to update the community on what we&amp;rsquo;ve got planned for Shoko and to give some clarification and possible updates on a few future projects &amp;amp; features that have been mentioned before on Discord. Its also important to note that not everything we discuss or bring up on Discord in regards to new features and improvements are actually planned for implementation. Sometimes its nothing more than just brainstorming and gauging reactions to said idea.</description></item><item><title>Kyoto Animation Fire</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/kyoto-animation-fire/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/kyoto-animation-fire/</guid><description>As many of you have probably already heard, Kyoto Animation, creators of such anime as Miss Kobayashi&amp;rsquo;s Dragon Maid, The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya, and A Silent Voice suffered a horrific arson attack yesterday that killed 33 people, with many more injured. This is the largest terror attack in Japan since 2001, and obviously extends far beyond the anime community.
American licensing company Sentai Filmworks have created a GoFundMe that we encourage all anime fans to donate to help those affected by this tragic event.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Wordpress Hello New Site</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/goodbye-wordpress-hello-new-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 02:45:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/goodbye-wordpress-hello-new-site/</guid><description>Welcome to the new Shoko Website!
While some members of our team having been working away on fixing issues created by the move to .NET Standard, we also started a side-project to create design and create a brand new website for Shoko. Up until now, we&amp;rsquo;ve always used WordPress to run our website and while it worked, there were definitely some limitations that started to become more apparent, especially with some of our future plans.</description></item><item><title>AniDB Needs Our Help</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/anidb-needs-our-help/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 01:44:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/anidb-needs-our-help/</guid><description>The amazing folks over at AniDB have recently announced that their hosting, which had provided for free for many years by a generous member will be coming to an end soon. While the AniDB team have found a replacement host, there is now an issue of how exactly they will pay for this host. AniDB has never once accepted donations or placed Ads on their website and have always provided their content to the masses for free which has been great for everyone.</description></item></channel></rss>