<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beta on Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/beta/</link><description>Recent content in Beta on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 21:32:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/beta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shoko Version 3.8 Beta</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-beta/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 21:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-beta/</guid><description>Hello Everyone!
After seven months of development, we&amp;rsquo;re close to releasing the next version of Shoko, Version 3.8! Looking back at our past releases, this upcoming version is by far the biggest release we&amp;rsquo;ve done so far. However with that being said, Version 3.8 is not really as feature packed as one might think based off the claim I just made, instead the majority of work has been to optimizing Server and Desktop code as these are essential to our overall goal of making Shoko Server cross-platform and the building of the new Shoko Desktop, currently codename ClientV2.</description></item><item><title>JMM is Now Shoko! Version 3.7 Beta</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 07:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over two months since the last blog post and the team has been hard at work on the next version, version 3.7. However as you can probably guess, besides continued development on the program, there have been quite a few other changes that have been made with the biggest being the new name.
Starting With Version 3.7, JMM Will Now be Known as Shoko. Over the past couple months, starting around mid-development of Version 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6 Beta Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-beta-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 07:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-beta-released/</guid><description>After completing our internal testing, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to release a public beta for the upcoming version 3.6!
If you take a look at the changelog you&amp;rsquo;ll see that a lot of work has gone into JMM version 3.6 with new features added, various improvements to existing features and functionality and fixing quite a few bugs. I&amp;rsquo;ve highlighted the two biggest changes and what the focus of this beta, however there are a lot of great additions with version 3.</description></item></channel></rss>