<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Downloads on Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/</link><description>Recent content in Downloads on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/downloads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My Anime 3</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/my-anime-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/my-anime-3/</guid><description>Bringing Your Anime To The Bigger Screen My Anime 3 is our oldest media streaming plugin and was the first anime plugin for media streaming programs to provide rich and detailed information. Before the times of Shoko and even JMM itself, My Anime 3 allowed users to get comfy on their couch, load up Media Portal and watch the most popular shows of 2008. Nowadays My Anime 3 offers the same TV watching experience while relying on Shoko to provide your collection and its detailed information.</description></item><item><title>Nakamori</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/nakamori/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/nakamori/</guid><description>Hello Kodi, Meet Nakamori Nakamori takes the versatility of Kodi and combines it with the power of Shoko to bring your anime collection to life. With complete integration you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about how your folders or files are named as Nakamori pulls all required information straight from Shoko. All you need to do is sit back, relax and knock some of that backlog out.
Device Agnostic Nakamori works on any device capable of running Kodi which means that $20 Raspberry Pi you bought last year now has a purpose besides collecting dust in your desk drawer.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Desktop</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-desktop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-desktop/</guid><description>Collection Management However You Want Users have complete control over every aspect of their collection with Shoko Desktop. Arrange and organize your collection in what ever manner suits you best so if you prefer Japanese names or want to group series by studio, go for it. This is your collection so why should anyone else decide how you view and manage it.
Educate Me Sensei We designed Shoko Desktop to be easy to use while still providing advanced features for our more tech savy users because more options are never a negative thing.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Metadata</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-metadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-metadata/</guid><description>Plex, Meet Your Newest Library Plex is one of the most popular user generated streaming service available so it only makes sense for Shoko, one of the best Anime cataloging programs to provide support for it. Now you too can stream your anime anywhere in the world on any device making those bathroom breaks even more enjoyable. You&amp;rsquo;re welcome. While Plex still handles all the heavy lifting (because its selfish like that), Shoko Metadata takes over the role of well, providing the metadata for the series and movies in your collection.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Server</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-server/</guid><description>Automation Done Right Manually manging your anime collection is hard work, tedious and extremely boring and frankly who has the time for that? With Shoko, regain your precious time back and instead spend it on debating on which series in your backlog you might watch before eventually deciding on watching a series you&amp;rsquo;ve already watched. We designed Shoko to be incredibly easy to install and takes less than five minutes to get it setup, running and cataloging your anime collection.</description></item><item><title>Shokofin</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shokofin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shokofin/</guid><description>Your Plex Alternative Plex is great, but sometimes you want something different and that&amp;rsquo;s where Jellyfin comes in.
Taking the versatility of Jellyfin and combing it with the automation of Shoko gives you the ability to watch your anime collection from any Jellyfin supported device.
Why Use Shokofin? Shokofin sends your watched state data back to Shoko allowing Shoko to update your linked community sites automatically so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to.</description></item></channel></rss>