<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My Anime 3 on Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/my-anime-3/</link><description>Recent content in My Anime 3 on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 18:09:21 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/my-anime-3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shoko 2021 Project Update</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-2021-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 18:09:21 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-2021-roadmap/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret our team is working on multiple projects under the Shoko umbrella. Some of them we&amp;rsquo;ve talked about publicly, either on this website, on Discord, and on other platforms, and some we&amp;rsquo;ve only discussed internall amongst the team. So with it being a new year, we thought it would be best to outline the current status on all of our projects, as well as talk about some new ones in development.</description></item><item><title>My Anime Version 3.7.3 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/my-anime-3-version-3-7-3-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 21:01:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/my-anime-3-version-3-7-3-released/</guid><description>After a couple weeks of testing we&amp;rsquo;re happy to release My Anime 3.7.3.
This maintenance release address some incompatibility issues when using the latest version of Shoko Server. Episodes lists should now properly populate and users should not encounter anymore playback issues.
If you continue to encounter any of these issues or discover a new issue, please create a issue on Github.
Contributors This release was made possible by the following people.</description></item><item><title>My Anime 3 Version 3.7.2 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/my-anime-3-version-3-7-2-released/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 21:01:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/my-anime-3-version-3-7-2-released/</guid><description>After a very long wait, the latest version of My Anime 3 is now available for download!
This releases address some long-standing issues and new issues created during various updates that were made to Shoko Server since the last My Anime 3 which was almost a year ago. While our original goal was to get this update out earlier this year, the lack of devs with experience using Media Portal and/or My Anime 3 caused this updated to get pushed back multiple times.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.8.2 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-2-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 12:04:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-2-released/</guid><description>Right in time for Christmas, Shoko Version 3.8.2 has been released!
This release was mainly focused on fixing bugs discovered since the previous release and making the entire Shoko process smoother and easier to use. Utilities now load much quicker and random quirks with tags, seasons and filters have been fixed. As always check the Changelog for a complete list of changes made.
My Anime 3 Support For Version 3.8 First, thank you to all our My Anime 3 users for being patient while waiting for this release, more work was needed then we realized to get My Anime 3 working with Shoko Version 3.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7.0.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-1-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 20:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-1-released/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve released a maintenance update, version 3.7.01 for the following programs/plugins.
Shoko Server Shoko Desktop My Anime 3 This maintenance update should resolve all migration issues, JMM uninstall issues and also includes some additional bug fixes. For a full list of changes please check the changelog. If you are still encountering any migration issues on 3.7.0.1, please contact us on Discord.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-released/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
While originally scheduled for earlier this month, Shoko Version 3.7 is finally available for download!
Version 3.7 is a big milestone for us for a variety of reasons that all share the same goal, to make Shoko even better for both users and developers. Shoko is open-source for a reason, we want people to contribute, to implement new ideas, fix bugs or even optimize the code. We truly appreciate each and every person that has contributed to the project and want to make it even more easier to do so by addressing some of the issues that have been brought up.</description></item><item><title>JMM is Now Shoko! Version 3.7 Beta</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 07:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over two months since the last blog post and the team has been hard at work on the next version, version 3.7. However as you can probably guess, besides continued development on the program, there have been quite a few other changes that have been made with the biggest being the new name.
Starting With Version 3.7, JMM Will Now be Known as Shoko. Over the past couple months, starting around mid-development of Version 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6 Brings Speed and Streaming</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-brings-speed-and-streaming/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 12:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-brings-speed-and-streaming/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
After a very successful beta that helped in identifying previously unknown issues and extended internal testing, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce that JMM Version 3.6.0.2 is available for download! Version 3.6 is by far the biggest update we&amp;rsquo;ve ever released containing over 40,000 lines of code added, changed and removed when compared to the previous version. While we generally try to limit the amount of new features added in the next version to reduce unforeseen issues, we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to hold back completed features and decided to do the extra work that was required to release this update.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6 Beta Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-beta-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 07:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-beta-released/</guid><description>After completing our internal testing, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to release a public beta for the upcoming version 3.6!
If you take a look at the changelog you&amp;rsquo;ll see that a lot of work has gone into JMM version 3.6 with new features added, various improvements to existing features and functionality and fixing quite a few bugs. I&amp;rsquo;ve highlighted the two biggest changes and what the focus of this beta, however there are a lot of great additions with version 3.</description></item></channel></rss>