<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/</link><description>Recent content on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shokofin 4.0.0 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shokofin-4-0-0-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shokofin-4-0-0-released/</guid><description>To the people expecting this to be just a small release to add support for Jellyfin 10.9; You were wrong. Sorry. 😔 Instead you&amp;rsquo;ll get this feature packed release that has been accumulating over the last year. If you don&amp;rsquo;t already know what Shokofin is, then I&amp;rsquo;ll advise you to read our introduction post, check out our docs or explore the GitHub repository first.
We have a new stable plugin repository URL, so update yours if you haven&amp;rsquo;t already!</description></item><item><title>Hello ShokoRelay</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/hello-shokorelay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 09:16:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/hello-shokorelay/</guid><description>As we continue our efforts on the next major update to Shoko itself, packed with new features and significant improvements, we&amp;rsquo;re excited to shine a spotlight on a new community Plex agent/scanner recently launched, called ShokoRelay.
What Is ShokoRelay? ShokoRelay originated as a fork/PR of Shoko Metadata, initially aimed at addressing missing features in the original software. However, as further adjustments were made, it underwent a transformative process, acquiring its own distinct functionalities.</description></item><item><title>Lets Talk Themes</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/lets-talk-themes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/lets-talk-themes/</guid><description>One of the oldest feature requests going all the way back to when the program was still called JMM, was the implementation of proper theme support for both Server and Desktop. Although it was explored, limitations related to WPF made this request near impossible and a huge time sink for the devs.
With the announcement of Shoko Desktop 2, its change from a C# program to a web application and the eventual decision to merge Shoko Desktop features into the Server Web UI.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 4.2.0 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-420-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 09:16:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-420-released/</guid><description>We are thrilled to announce the release of the latest version of Shoko! This new version introduces numerous enhancements, novel features, and bug fixes that improve the user experience significantly.
For a comprehensive list of changes, kindly visit our Changelog.
Basic ARM64 Support Thanks to Mohan226, we&amp;rsquo;re now able to offer an ARM64 build of Shoko on Linux
However, please note that all initial testing was conducted in a virtual machine.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 4.1.2 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-1-2-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 13:16:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-1-2-released/</guid><description>We are pleased to announce another maintenance release! In this release, we have fixed several reported bugs and issues that arose while working on the Jellyfin plugin, Shokofin, as well as made significant improvements to version 3 of our API.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.
Shoko Development We understand that our lack of frequent updates has been a source of concern, and we have been asked about it numerous times.</description></item><item><title>Nakamori 4.1.0 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/nakamori-4-1-0-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 12:04:35 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/nakamori-4-1-0-released/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the latest version of Nakamori is now available for download, after undergoing many months of internal and public testing. This update is one of the most significant to date, as Nakamori has been entirely rewritten from the ground up to shift to Python 3 with Kodi 19.
However, due to the Kodi dev team&amp;rsquo;s decision, Nakamori is no longer backwards compatible with older versions of Kodi.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 4.1.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-1-1-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 15:20:53 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-1-1-released/</guid><description>This maintenance release addresses a few reported bugs and a few under-the-hood changes that won&amp;rsquo;t affect most users. However, its main purpose is it allows Shoko Server to work with our latest media player plugin, Shokofin. Read the announcement blog post about Shokofin if you&amp;rsquo;d like to learn more.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.
We also figured this blog post would be a good time to update everyone on the status of our in-development projects.</description></item><item><title>Hello Shokofin</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/hello-shokofin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/hello-shokofin/</guid><description>After being in development for quite some time, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce our Jellyfin plugin is now available to all users. We&amp;rsquo;ve previously talked about Shokofin before and with a starting version of 1.4.7, some of you might be wondering why it took so long for us to announce it.
Originally we had to wait for Jellyfin version 10.7 to be released, as we heavily relied on a change introduced in that version and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to make people install a dev version that could potentially cause damage to their database.</description></item><item><title>Shoko 2021 Project Update</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-2021-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 18:09:21 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-2021-roadmap/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret our team is working on multiple projects under the Shoko umbrella. Some of them we&amp;rsquo;ve talked about publicly, either on this website, on Discord, and on other platforms, and some we&amp;rsquo;ve only discussed internall amongst the team. So with it being a new year, we thought it would be best to outline the current status on all of our projects, as well as talk about some new ones in development.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 4.1.0 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-1-0-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 12:23:34 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-1-0-released/</guid><description>Kicking off 2021 with the next release of Shoko, Shoko Version 4.1.0 is available for download!
This release focused primarily on a lot of much needed refactoring and backend changes and while not as jam packed as our normal releases tend to be. A lot of work done will help with the development of some major changes Shoko will be undergoing in 2021.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Docs Refresh</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-refresh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 02:34:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-refresh/</guid><description>After nearly five months, multiple designs and iterations, our new design for Shoko Docs is up! The main goal of this update was to make the design similar to the updated homepage as well as reevaluate the existing content as a lot of the information had become outdated or simply incorrect. To that end most of the content was rewritten and condensed to not only make it easier to follow, but create less confusion for future contributors.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Sushi.Net</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-sushi.net/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 19:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-sushi.net/</guid><description>While we continue working on the next release of Shoko (coming soon!), one of our devs has been working on a side-project for some time now and has released a public beta which we wanted to highlight and what better time than right before we say goodbye to 2020 and hello to 2021.
Introducing Sushi.Net, A .NET Port of Sushi For those not familiar, sushi is a Python script that allows you to remux releases with ease regardless of audio and/or subtitle source.</description></item><item><title>Meet Ashen, Our New Hashing Service</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/meet-ashen/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 17:24:19 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/meet-ashen/</guid><description>For a while now, one of the main concerns of the Shoko team is our current reliance on select metadata providers to the point where if a crucial metadata provider like AniDB or TvDB were to cut off access, Shoko itself would lose critical functions. To remedy this situation, we&amp;rsquo;ve been looking into alternative metadata sources and are happy to announce our partnership with animeshon, an upcoming anime &amp;amp; manga metadata provider and their perceptual hashing service Ashen.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Metadata 1.5 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-metadata-1.5-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:13:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-metadata-1.5-released/</guid><description>It has been a whole year since the last release! The focus of this release fixes an issue with subdirectories, now you can store your anime in whatever way you want without having to put up with Plex and its non-anime friendly folder structure. This release also adds a few user requested features such as single season ordering which you can read about below..
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 4.0.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-0-1-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:06:42 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-0-1-released/</guid><description>This small maintenance release addresses a bug introduced in version 4.0.0 that caused imported files to automatically be renamed regardless of user preference. As this was an unscheduled release, expect another maintenance update in the next week or so to address a few minor bugs such as Plex linking inconsistencies and TVDB cache related issues.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.
Fixing Renamed Files For users affected by this bug, we&amp;rsquo;ve created a renamer plugin to restore your filenames.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 4.0.0 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-0-0-released/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 09:08:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-0-0-released/</guid><description>After months of work we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce that Shoko version 4.0.0 is available for download! This releases introduce some big changes for Shoko, especially for our Windows users, so we recommend reading through this release post before updating.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.
.NET Core Conversion We&amp;rsquo;ve successfully converted Shoko Server to .NET Core, providing better cross compatibility support, as well as making Shoko easier to build upon and maintain as we go forward.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Website Updated</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-website-updated/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 01:12:14 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-website-updated/</guid><description>While in the works for a few months now, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to launch the latest version of the Shoko Website bringing a refreshed look and a few new additions. As usual, our Discord users have gotten glimpses into the new site as it&amp;rsquo;s progressed through different iterations to finally become what you&amp;rsquo;re currently looking at.
Lets go over a few of the changes and provide some insight on what the next couple of months have in store for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.9.7 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-7-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 15:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-7-released/</guid><description>Shoko Version 3.9.7 is now available for download!
We&amp;rsquo;ve been hard at on some of the items we previously mentioned in What&amp;rsquo;s Next For Shoko and wanted to release this feature packed release as it might be awhile before the next release.
This release contains many fixes and improvements to the AniDB system, TvDB System and TvDB image downloading. We&amp;rsquo;ve also tweaked the Sentry settings to stop it from spamming the logs.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.9.6 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-6-released/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-6-released/</guid><description>Shoko Version 3.9.6 is now available for download!
This release addresses various startup and crashing bugs reported after the initial release of version 3.9.5. If any user continues to experience any startup or crashing related issues, please let us know.
This releases also addresses the changes The TvDB has made to their API. Episode images and Fanart should properly download again.
As always you can find a summary of the changes made by checking out the Changelog.</description></item><item><title>My Anime Version 3.7.3 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/my-anime-3-version-3-7-3-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 21:01:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/my-anime-3-version-3-7-3-released/</guid><description>After a couple weeks of testing we&amp;rsquo;re happy to release My Anime 3.7.3.
This maintenance release address some incompatibility issues when using the latest version of Shoko Server. Episodes lists should now properly populate and users should not encounter anymore playback issues.
If you continue to encounter any of these issues or discover a new issue, please create a issue on Github.
Contributors This release was made possible by the following people.</description></item><item><title>Whats Next for Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/whats-next-for-shoko/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/whats-next-for-shoko/</guid><description>As mentioned earlier this week, we wanted to update the community on what we&amp;rsquo;ve got planned for Shoko and to give some clarification and possible updates on a few future projects &amp;amp; features that have been mentioned before on Discord. Its also important to note that not everything we discuss or bring up on Discord in regards to new features and improvements are actually planned for implementation. Sometimes its nothing more than just brainstorming and gauging reactions to said idea.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.9.5 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-5-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-5-released/</guid><description>Shoko Version 3.9.5 is now available for download!
This release addresses various bugs reported since the last update that we felt needed addressing while we continue working on the next major version of Shoko. As always you can find a summary of the changes made by checking out the Changelog.
What&amp;rsquo;s Next For Shoko We get asked quite often what&amp;rsquo;s being worked on at the moment or when a certain feature that&amp;rsquo;s been mentioned before will be released.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Docs Updated</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-updated/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 17:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-updated/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been on our Discord server lately you&amp;rsquo;ve might of seen us asking for feedback on a new design we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on for Shoko Docs. With the feedback &amp;amp; suggestions we received from the community we&amp;rsquo;re happy to launch the latest version of Shoko Docs!
In the past to save time, we used a prebuilt template and customized it to our needs. While this worked in the beginning, we found that trying to add or modify the template outside of its designed purpose would cause issues.</description></item><item><title>Kyoto Animation Fire</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/kyoto-animation-fire/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/kyoto-animation-fire/</guid><description>As many of you have probably already heard, Kyoto Animation, creators of such anime as Miss Kobayashi&amp;rsquo;s Dragon Maid, The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya, and A Silent Voice suffered a horrific arson attack yesterday that killed 33 people, with many more injured. This is the largest terror attack in Japan since 2001, and obviously extends far beyond the anime community.
American licensing company Sentai Filmworks have created a GoFundMe that we encourage all anime fans to donate to help those affected by this tragic event.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.9.4 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-4-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-4-released/</guid><description>Shoko Version 3.9.4 is now available for download!
This release addresses various bugs reported since the last update that we felt needed addressing before the next major version. This version also contains a big change which we&amp;rsquo;ve addressed below.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.
Shoko Analytics One of the bigger changes we were going to introduce in version 4.0 was the inclusion of a telemetry service.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Wordpress Hello New Site</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/goodbye-wordpress-hello-new-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 02:45:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/goodbye-wordpress-hello-new-site/</guid><description>Welcome to the new Shoko Website!
While some members of our team having been working away on fixing issues created by the move to .NET Standard, we also started a side-project to create design and create a brand new website for Shoko. Up until now, we&amp;rsquo;ve always used WordPress to run our website and while it worked, there were definitely some limitations that started to become more apparent, especially with some of our future plans.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.9.3 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-3-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 19:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-3-released/</guid><description>Shoko Version 3.9.3 is now available for download!
This release address an issue with manually linked files not updating properly on AniDB as well as additional fixes regarding manually linking. For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.
Download Link Download Shoko Version 3.9.3
Contributors This release was made possible by the following people.
BigRetroMike, Cazzar &amp;amp; Da3dsoul</description></item><item><title>My Anime 3 Version 3.7.2 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/my-anime-3-version-3-7-2-released/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 21:01:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/my-anime-3-version-3-7-2-released/</guid><description>After a very long wait, the latest version of My Anime 3 is now available for download!
This releases address some long-standing issues and new issues created during various updates that were made to Shoko Server since the last My Anime 3 which was almost a year ago. While our original goal was to get this update out earlier this year, the lack of devs with experience using Media Portal and/or My Anime 3 caused this updated to get pushed back multiple times.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.9.2 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-2-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 10:57:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-2-released/</guid><description>Shoko Version 3.9.2 is now available for download!
This release address an issue with searching in Shoko Desktop, we wanted to get this out before merging in the work being done on the .NET Standard conversion. Contributors This release was made possible by the following people. Da3dsoul</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.9.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-1-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 23:20:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-1-released/</guid><description>Shoko Version 3.9.1 is now available for download!
We&amp;rsquo;ve made a few visual changes to the TvDB Linking system but beyond that, this is mostly a maintenance release addressing some issues that were discovered when attempting to update your AniDB MyList.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.
Unless there are any major issues discovered after this release, this will be the last release in the 3.9.X series as we&amp;rsquo;ll be working on some major changes going forward.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.9.0 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-0-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 20:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-9-0-released/</guid><description>After a couple months of extensive testing, the latest version of Shoko has been released!
This release contains a lot of new and updated features and bug fixes making it one of our biggest updates in quite some time. While we initially tried to stay away from big releases, some outside factors such as MAL unexpectedly shutting down their API (more below) and our revamped TvDB Linking System delayed this release.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.8.3 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-3-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 01:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-3-released/</guid><description>This release will be the last release for version 3.8 as we&amp;rsquo;re starting to work on some major internal changes that we&amp;rsquo;ve been planning for awhile. There are a couple features and issues we wanted to address for this release but we&amp;rsquo;re unable to, as such they will be included in the next major release which currently has no date.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.</description></item><item><title>AniDB Needs Our Help</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/anidb-needs-our-help/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 01:44:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/anidb-needs-our-help/</guid><description>The amazing folks over at AniDB have recently announced that their hosting, which had provided for free for many years by a generous member will be coming to an end soon. While the AniDB team have found a replacement host, there is now an issue of how exactly they will pay for this host. AniDB has never once accepted donations or placed Ads on their website and have always provided their content to the masses for free which has been great for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.8.2 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-2-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 12:04:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-2-released/</guid><description>Right in time for Christmas, Shoko Version 3.8.2 has been released!
This release was mainly focused on fixing bugs discovered since the previous release and making the entire Shoko process smoother and easier to use. Utilities now load much quicker and random quirks with tags, seasons and filters have been fixed. As always check the Changelog for a complete list of changes made.
My Anime 3 Support For Version 3.8 First, thank you to all our My Anime 3 users for being patient while waiting for this release, more work was needed then we realized to get My Anime 3 working with Shoko Version 3.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.8.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-1-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 19:54:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-1-released/</guid><description>Almost a month later and we&amp;rsquo;re back with another update!
Version 3.8 was our biggest release to date and was released a very long time after Version 3.7. We&amp;rsquo;ve decided that going forward we&amp;rsquo;re going to aim for releasing updates at least once a month to ease migration for current users and reduce the amount of testing needed beforehand. We&amp;rsquo;ve also made some changes to our versioning system which we&amp;rsquo;ve outlined below.</description></item><item><title>Anime Buddy Discontinued</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/anime-buddy-discontinued/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 03:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/anime-buddy-discontinued/</guid><description>We have received numerous inquiries about the development status of Anime Buddy in the last few months. Initially, we intended to continue updating the software, but several issues have made it nearly impossible for us to do so without creating a completely new program. Anime Buddy has not received any updates in years, and with the significant changes we&amp;rsquo;ve implemented in recent versions, we would need to rewrite the entire program to make it functional again.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.8 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 21:18:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-released/</guid><description>After eight very long months, we’re pleased to announce that Shoko Version 3.8 is available for download!
While we’ve added quite a few new features, fixed a lot of bugs and updated a lot of existing features and functionality, the main reason this release took longer than usual is due to the giant refactoring we did on the Shoko codebase. The great thing about this refactor is that everyone benefits from it.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.8 Beta</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-beta/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 21:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-beta/</guid><description>Hello Everyone!
After seven months of development, we&amp;rsquo;re close to releasing the next version of Shoko, Version 3.8! Looking back at our past releases, this upcoming version is by far the biggest release we&amp;rsquo;ve done so far. However with that being said, Version 3.8 is not really as feature packed as one might think based off the claim I just made, instead the majority of work has been to optimizing Server and Desktop code as these are essential to our overall goal of making Shoko Server cross-platform and the building of the new Shoko Desktop, currently codename ClientV2.</description></item><item><title>Announcing a New Plugin - ShokoMetadata</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/announcing-a-new-plugin-shokometadata/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 04:15:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/announcing-a-new-plugin-shokometadata/</guid><description>For the last couple of weeks, Cazzar has been working on a new Plex plugin called, Shoko Metadata.
There recently has been the release for version 1.0.0 as this has been deemed the latest stable version working alongside Shoko Server 3.7.0.4. Though at the time of writing, the current version has little documentation due to being an early release.
What is it? Firstly, I should get into what this does. Simply put, this plugin for Plex allows you to have the series information for your libraries, as well as tagging derived from the AniDB tags.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7.0.4 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-4-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 03:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-4-released/</guid><description>We’ve released a maintenance update, version 3.7.0.4 for the following programs/plugins.
Shoko Server Shoko Desktop Shoko on Plex This maintenance update focuses on fixing various bugs that have been reported since we released 3.7.0.0. Assuming there are no new program breaking bugs, this will be the last maintenance release for this cycle. Also please be aware, while Shoko on Plex is listed as being updated, there is no new plugin to download as all of its changes were done in Shoko Server.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Shoko Docs</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-shoko-docs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 19:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-shoko-docs/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re Back!
This past weekend we moved everything over to our ShokoAnime domain name making it our primary domain name and switched to a more reliable hosts. You may of noticed some changes around the site, during the downtime the site went through some intensive maintenance stripping away anything that was causing performance issues. We also decided to go for a less resource intensive theme that&amp;rsquo;s sleeker and for those of you visiting us on mobile, it looks great.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7.0.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-1-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 20:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-1-released/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve released a maintenance update, version 3.7.01 for the following programs/plugins.
Shoko Server Shoko Desktop My Anime 3 This maintenance update should resolve all migration issues, JMM uninstall issues and also includes some additional bug fixes. For a full list of changes please check the changelog. If you are still encountering any migration issues on 3.7.0.1, please contact us on Discord.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-released/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
While originally scheduled for earlier this month, Shoko Version 3.7 is finally available for download!
Version 3.7 is a big milestone for us for a variety of reasons that all share the same goal, to make Shoko even better for both users and developers. Shoko is open-source for a reason, we want people to contribute, to implement new ideas, fix bugs or even optimize the code. We truly appreciate each and every person that has contributed to the project and want to make it even more easier to do so by addressing some of the issues that have been brought up.</description></item><item><title>JMM is Now Shoko! Version 3.7 Beta</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 07:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over two months since the last blog post and the team has been hard at work on the next version, version 3.7. However as you can probably guess, besides continued development on the program, there have been quite a few other changes that have been made with the biggest being the new name.
Starting With Version 3.7, JMM Will Now be Known as Shoko. Over the past couple months, starting around mid-development of Version 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6.0.3 Fixing Yesterdays Problems Today</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-0-3-fixing-yesterdays-problems-today/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-0-3-fixing-yesterdays-problems-today/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve released a maintenance update for JMM, version 3.6.0.3 that fixes JMM Server and Desktop crashing that was reported shortly after the release of 3.6.0.2. Just goes to show that even with a month long public beta and rigorous internal testing all it takes is that one unique setup to present us with a bug we never encountered.
Download links have been updated, you can also check the changelog for additional information.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6 Brings Speed and Streaming</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-brings-speed-and-streaming/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 12:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-brings-speed-and-streaming/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
After a very successful beta that helped in identifying previously unknown issues and extended internal testing, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce that JMM Version 3.6.0.2 is available for download! Version 3.6 is by far the biggest update we&amp;rsquo;ve ever released containing over 40,000 lines of code added, changed and removed when compared to the previous version. While we generally try to limit the amount of new features added in the next version to reduce unforeseen issues, we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to hold back completed features and decided to do the extra work that was required to release this update.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the JMM Server Web UI</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-the-jmm-server-webui/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 11:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-the-jmm-server-webui/</guid><description>One of the main goals for JMM is to make the programs and plugins as accessible to as many people as possible regardless of operating system. This has been a goal of the project for a very long time but has seen minimal progress, until today as we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce that we&amp;rsquo;re now one step closer to making this goal a reality.
We&amp;rsquo;d like to introduce everyone to out newest project, the JMM Server Web UI which you can see in the screenshot above.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6 Beta Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-beta-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 07:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-beta-released/</guid><description>After completing our internal testing, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to release a public beta for the upcoming version 3.6!
If you take a look at the changelog you&amp;rsquo;ll see that a lot of work has gone into JMM version 3.6 with new features added, various improvements to existing features and functionality and fixing quite a few bugs. I&amp;rsquo;ve highlighted the two biggest changes and what the focus of this beta, however there are a lot of great additions with version 3.</description></item><item><title>Translation is a Go</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/translation-is-a-go/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 09:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/translation-is-a-go/</guid><description>After a short delay and some additional testing, we&amp;rsquo;re now ready to start accepting user translations to replace our current machine translations! We&amp;rsquo;ll be using Google Sheets to host the .xlsx file that contains all the language strings. We believe it&amp;rsquo;s the easiest and most efficient method available to allow anyone the opportunity to help translate JMM without having to know how to use Visual Studio or edit .resx files.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.5.0.2 Maintenance Update</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-5-0-2-maintenance-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 08:37:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-5-0-2-maintenance-update/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve discovered a bug with our installer script that caused required files to not be included during the build process. We&amp;rsquo;ve released an update to fix this issue, all users who previously installed version 3.5.0.1 should download this release.
We&amp;rsquo;ve also pulled the latest version of Shoko on Plex and replaced it with the previous version while we investigate some newly discovered bugs.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.5.0.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-5-0-1-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 12:33:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-5-0-1-released/</guid><description>UPDATE: If JMM Server will not start for you please re-download version 3.5.0.1. The initial upload was missing a .dll file that has since been added.
After a very successful beta, JMM version 3.5.0.1 is available for download!
Before I go into the details of what&amp;rsquo;s new, we&amp;rsquo;d like to thank everyone that participated in the 3.5 beta. We received a lot of feedback that helped improve JMM with changes made and bugs discovered and fixed as a direct result.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.6.4 Brings a New Site</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-4-6-4-brings-a-new-site/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 10:44:55 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-4-6-4-brings-a-new-site/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
JMM has gone through a lot of changes over the past couple of months, both with JMM itself and as you might of noticed, the website as well. Before I go into detail about the new website and other changes lets talk about the new version of JMM!
With each release, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover a few of the new additions or changes but for a complete listing, check out the changelog.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.4.3 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-4-4-3-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 03:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-4-4-3-released/</guid><description>Version 3.4.4 introduces the following changes, we recommend reading through this blog post in order to familiarize yourself with what&amp;rsquo;s changed.
Metro Dashboard The series display in the Metro dashboard has received a few small tweaks.
A button has been added to refresh this series The previous episode you watch is now shown, so you can re-watch it easily, or just in case you accidentally marked it as watched The next episode to watch is highlighted and shows a few more details than other episodes Trakt The major focus of this release has been adding support for Version 2.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://shokoanime.com/jsonfeed/index.json</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/jsonfeed/index.json</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://shokoanime.com/index.json</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/index.json</guid><description/></item><item><title>About Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/about/</guid><description>The Team
[ContentBlock]
From a small AniDB Mylist program to a full blown client-server architecture program. These are the people that made it happen and continue to improve it.
[ContentBlock]
Click on a team member for more information on them.
[ContentBlock]
The Early Years
[ContentBlock]
In July of 2006, lwerndly publicly released his personal AniDB client, AniDB Monitor giving AniDB members the ability to automatically hash their files for comparison, add them to their AniDB Mylist and allowed users to update their episode watched states with ease.</description></item><item><title>My Anime 3</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/my-anime-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/my-anime-3/</guid><description>Bringing Your Anime To The Bigger Screen My Anime 3 is our oldest media streaming plugin and was the first anime plugin for media streaming programs to provide rich and detailed information. Before the times of Shoko and even JMM itself, My Anime 3 allowed users to get comfy on their couch, load up Media Portal and watch the most popular shows of 2008. Nowadays My Anime 3 offers the same TV watching experience while relying on Shoko to provide your collection and its detailed information.</description></item><item><title>Nakamori</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/nakamori/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/nakamori/</guid><description>Hello Kodi, Meet Nakamori Nakamori takes the versatility of Kodi and combines it with the power of Shoko to bring your anime collection to life. With complete integration you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about how your folders or files are named as Nakamori pulls all required information straight from Shoko. All you need to do is sit back, relax and knock some of that backlog out.
Device Agnostic Nakamori works on any device capable of running Kodi which means that $20 Raspberry Pi you bought last year now has a purpose besides collecting dust in your desk drawer.</description></item><item><title>Search Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/search/</guid><description>Input Search Criteria Below The embedded Google Search below will allow you to search through the Shoko website and Shoko Docs.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Desktop</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-desktop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-desktop/</guid><description>Collection Management However You Want Users have complete control over every aspect of their collection with Shoko Desktop. Arrange and organize your collection in what ever manner suits you best so if you prefer Japanese names or want to group series by studio, go for it. This is your collection so why should anyone else decide how you view and manage it.
Educate Me Sensei We designed Shoko Desktop to be easy to use while still providing advanced features for our more tech savy users because more options are never a negative thing.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Metadata</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-metadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-metadata/</guid><description>Plex, Meet Your Newest Library Plex is one of the most popular user generated streaming service available so it only makes sense for Shoko, one of the best Anime cataloging programs to provide support for it. Now you too can stream your anime anywhere in the world on any device making those bathroom breaks even more enjoyable. You&amp;rsquo;re welcome. While Plex still handles all the heavy lifting (because its selfish like that), Shoko Metadata takes over the role of well, providing the metadata for the series and movies in your collection.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Server</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shoko-server/</guid><description>Automation Done Right Manually manging your anime collection is hard work, tedious and extremely boring and frankly who has the time for that? With Shoko, regain your precious time back and instead spend it on debating on which series in your backlog you might watch before eventually deciding on watching a series you&amp;rsquo;ve already watched. We designed Shoko to be incredibly easy to install and takes less than five minutes to get it setup, running and cataloging your anime collection.</description></item><item><title>Shokofin</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shokofin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/downloads/shokofin/</guid><description>Your Plex Alternative Plex is great, but sometimes you want something different and that&amp;rsquo;s where Jellyfin comes in.
Taking the versatility of Jellyfin and combing it with the automation of Shoko gives you the ability to watch your anime collection from any Jellyfin supported device.
Why Use Shokofin? Shokofin sends your watched state data back to Shoko allowing Shoko to update your linked community sites automatically so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to.</description></item></channel></rss>