<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General on Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/category/general/</link><description>Recent content in General on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 18:09:21 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/blog/category/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shoko 2021 Project Update</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-2021-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 18:09:21 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-2021-roadmap/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret our team is working on multiple projects under the Shoko umbrella. Some of them we&amp;rsquo;ve talked about publicly, either on this website, on Discord, and on other platforms, and some we&amp;rsquo;ve only discussed internall amongst the team. So with it being a new year, we thought it would be best to outline the current status on all of our projects, as well as talk about some new ones in development.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Sushi.Net</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-sushi.net/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 19:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-sushi.net/</guid><description>While we continue working on the next release of Shoko (coming soon!), one of our devs has been working on a side-project for some time now and has released a public beta which we wanted to highlight and what better time than right before we say goodbye to 2020 and hello to 2021.
Introducing Sushi.Net, A .NET Port of Sushi For those not familiar, sushi is a Python script that allows you to remux releases with ease regardless of audio and/or subtitle source.</description></item><item><title>Meet Ashen, Our New Hashing Service</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/meet-ashen/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 17:24:19 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/meet-ashen/</guid><description>For a while now, one of the main concerns of the Shoko team is our current reliance on select metadata providers to the point where if a crucial metadata provider like AniDB or TvDB were to cut off access, Shoko itself would lose critical functions. To remedy this situation, we&amp;rsquo;ve been looking into alternative metadata sources and are happy to announce our partnership with animeshon, an upcoming anime &amp;amp; manga metadata provider and their perceptual hashing service Ashen.</description></item><item><title>Whats Next for Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/whats-next-for-shoko/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/whats-next-for-shoko/</guid><description>As mentioned earlier this week, we wanted to update the community on what we&amp;rsquo;ve got planned for Shoko and to give some clarification and possible updates on a few future projects &amp;amp; features that have been mentioned before on Discord. Its also important to note that not everything we discuss or bring up on Discord in regards to new features and improvements are actually planned for implementation. Sometimes its nothing more than just brainstorming and gauging reactions to said idea.</description></item><item><title>Kyoto Animation Fire</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/kyoto-animation-fire/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/kyoto-animation-fire/</guid><description>As many of you have probably already heard, Kyoto Animation, creators of such anime as Miss Kobayashi&amp;rsquo;s Dragon Maid, The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya, and A Silent Voice suffered a horrific arson attack yesterday that killed 33 people, with many more injured. This is the largest terror attack in Japan since 2001, and obviously extends far beyond the anime community.
American licensing company Sentai Filmworks have created a GoFundMe that we encourage all anime fans to donate to help those affected by this tragic event.</description></item><item><title>AniDB Needs Our Help</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/anidb-needs-our-help/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 01:44:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/anidb-needs-our-help/</guid><description>The amazing folks over at AniDB have recently announced that their hosting, which had provided for free for many years by a generous member will be coming to an end soon. While the AniDB team have found a replacement host, there is now an issue of how exactly they will pay for this host. AniDB has never once accepted donations or placed Ads on their website and have always provided their content to the masses for free which has been great for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7.0.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-1-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 20:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-1-released/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve released a maintenance update, version 3.7.01 for the following programs/plugins.
Shoko Server Shoko Desktop My Anime 3 This maintenance update should resolve all migration issues, JMM uninstall issues and also includes some additional bug fixes. For a full list of changes please check the changelog. If you are still encountering any migration issues on 3.7.0.1, please contact us on Discord.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-released/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
While originally scheduled for earlier this month, Shoko Version 3.7 is finally available for download!
Version 3.7 is a big milestone for us for a variety of reasons that all share the same goal, to make Shoko even better for both users and developers. Shoko is open-source for a reason, we want people to contribute, to implement new ideas, fix bugs or even optimize the code. We truly appreciate each and every person that has contributed to the project and want to make it even more easier to do so by addressing some of the issues that have been brought up.</description></item><item><title>JMM is Now Shoko! Version 3.7 Beta</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 07:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over two months since the last blog post and the team has been hard at work on the next version, version 3.7. However as you can probably guess, besides continued development on the program, there have been quite a few other changes that have been made with the biggest being the new name.
Starting With Version 3.7, JMM Will Now be Known as Shoko. Over the past couple months, starting around mid-development of Version 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6.0.3 Fixing Yesterdays Problems Today</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-0-3-fixing-yesterdays-problems-today/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-0-3-fixing-yesterdays-problems-today/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve released a maintenance update for JMM, version 3.6.0.3 that fixes JMM Server and Desktop crashing that was reported shortly after the release of 3.6.0.2. Just goes to show that even with a month long public beta and rigorous internal testing all it takes is that one unique setup to present us with a bug we never encountered.
Download links have been updated, you can also check the changelog for additional information.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6 Brings Speed and Streaming</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-brings-speed-and-streaming/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 12:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-brings-speed-and-streaming/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
After a very successful beta that helped in identifying previously unknown issues and extended internal testing, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce that JMM Version 3.6.0.2 is available for download! Version 3.6 is by far the biggest update we&amp;rsquo;ve ever released containing over 40,000 lines of code added, changed and removed when compared to the previous version. While we generally try to limit the amount of new features added in the next version to reduce unforeseen issues, we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to hold back completed features and decided to do the extra work that was required to release this update.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the JMM Server Web UI</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-the-jmm-server-webui/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 11:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-the-jmm-server-webui/</guid><description>One of the main goals for JMM is to make the programs and plugins as accessible to as many people as possible regardless of operating system. This has been a goal of the project for a very long time but has seen minimal progress, until today as we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce that we&amp;rsquo;re now one step closer to making this goal a reality.
We&amp;rsquo;d like to introduce everyone to out newest project, the JMM Server Web UI which you can see in the screenshot above.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6 Beta Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-beta-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 07:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-beta-released/</guid><description>After completing our internal testing, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to release a public beta for the upcoming version 3.6!
If you take a look at the changelog you&amp;rsquo;ll see that a lot of work has gone into JMM version 3.6 with new features added, various improvements to existing features and functionality and fixing quite a few bugs. I&amp;rsquo;ve highlighted the two biggest changes and what the focus of this beta, however there are a lot of great additions with version 3.</description></item><item><title>Translation is a Go</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/translation-is-a-go/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 09:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/translation-is-a-go/</guid><description>After a short delay and some additional testing, we&amp;rsquo;re now ready to start accepting user translations to replace our current machine translations! We&amp;rsquo;ll be using Google Sheets to host the .xlsx file that contains all the language strings. We believe it&amp;rsquo;s the easiest and most efficient method available to allow anyone the opportunity to help translate JMM without having to know how to use Visual Studio or edit .resx files.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.5.0.2 Maintenance Update</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-5-0-2-maintenance-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 08:37:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-5-0-2-maintenance-update/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve discovered a bug with our installer script that caused required files to not be included during the build process. We&amp;rsquo;ve released an update to fix this issue, all users who previously installed version 3.5.0.1 should download this release.
We&amp;rsquo;ve also pulled the latest version of Shoko on Plex and replaced it with the previous version while we investigate some newly discovered bugs.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.6.4 Brings a New Site</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-4-6-4-brings-a-new-site/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 10:44:55 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-4-6-4-brings-a-new-site/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
JMM has gone through a lot of changes over the past couple of months, both with JMM itself and as you might of noticed, the website as well. Before I go into detail about the new website and other changes lets talk about the new version of JMM!
With each release, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover a few of the new additions or changes but for a complete listing, check out the changelog.</description></item></channel></rss>