<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Website on Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/category/website/</link><description>Recent content in Website on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 02:34:25 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/blog/category/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shoko Docs Refresh</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-refresh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 02:34:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-refresh/</guid><description>After nearly five months, multiple designs and iterations, our new design for Shoko Docs is up! The main goal of this update was to make the design similar to the updated homepage as well as reevaluate the existing content as a lot of the information had become outdated or simply incorrect. To that end most of the content was rewritten and condensed to not only make it easier to follow, but create less confusion for future contributors.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Website Updated</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-website-updated/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 01:12:14 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-website-updated/</guid><description>While in the works for a few months now, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to launch the latest version of the Shoko Website bringing a refreshed look and a few new additions. As usual, our Discord users have gotten glimpses into the new site as it&amp;rsquo;s progressed through different iterations to finally become what you&amp;rsquo;re currently looking at.
Lets go over a few of the changes and provide some insight on what the next couple of months have in store for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Whats Next for Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/whats-next-for-shoko/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/whats-next-for-shoko/</guid><description>As mentioned earlier this week, we wanted to update the community on what we&amp;rsquo;ve got planned for Shoko and to give some clarification and possible updates on a few future projects &amp;amp; features that have been mentioned before on Discord. Its also important to note that not everything we discuss or bring up on Discord in regards to new features and improvements are actually planned for implementation. Sometimes its nothing more than just brainstorming and gauging reactions to said idea.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Docs Updated</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-updated/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 17:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-updated/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been on our Discord server lately you&amp;rsquo;ve might of seen us asking for feedback on a new design we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on for Shoko Docs. With the feedback &amp;amp; suggestions we received from the community we&amp;rsquo;re happy to launch the latest version of Shoko Docs!
In the past to save time, we used a prebuilt template and customized it to our needs. While this worked in the beginning, we found that trying to add or modify the template outside of its designed purpose would cause issues.</description></item><item><title>Kyoto Animation Fire</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/kyoto-animation-fire/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/kyoto-animation-fire/</guid><description>As many of you have probably already heard, Kyoto Animation, creators of such anime as Miss Kobayashi&amp;rsquo;s Dragon Maid, The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya, and A Silent Voice suffered a horrific arson attack yesterday that killed 33 people, with many more injured. This is the largest terror attack in Japan since 2001, and obviously extends far beyond the anime community.
American licensing company Sentai Filmworks have created a GoFundMe that we encourage all anime fans to donate to help those affected by this tragic event.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Wordpress Hello New Site</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/goodbye-wordpress-hello-new-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 02:45:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/goodbye-wordpress-hello-new-site/</guid><description>Welcome to the new Shoko Website!
While some members of our team having been working away on fixing issues created by the move to .NET Standard, we also started a side-project to create design and create a brand new website for Shoko. Up until now, we&amp;rsquo;ve always used WordPress to run our website and while it worked, there were definitely some limitations that started to become more apparent, especially with some of our future plans.</description></item><item><title>AniDB Needs Our Help</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/anidb-needs-our-help/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 01:44:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/anidb-needs-our-help/</guid><description>The amazing folks over at AniDB have recently announced that their hosting, which had provided for free for many years by a generous member will be coming to an end soon. While the AniDB team have found a replacement host, there is now an issue of how exactly they will pay for this host. AniDB has never once accepted donations or placed Ads on their website and have always provided their content to the masses for free which has been great for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Shoko Docs</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-shoko-docs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 19:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-shoko-docs/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re Back!
This past weekend we moved everything over to our ShokoAnime domain name making it our primary domain name and switched to a more reliable hosts. You may of noticed some changes around the site, during the downtime the site went through some intensive maintenance stripping away anything that was causing performance issues. We also decided to go for a less resource intensive theme that&amp;rsquo;s sleeker and for those of you visiting us on mobile, it looks great.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-released/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
While originally scheduled for earlier this month, Shoko Version 3.7 is finally available for download!
Version 3.7 is a big milestone for us for a variety of reasons that all share the same goal, to make Shoko even better for both users and developers. Shoko is open-source for a reason, we want people to contribute, to implement new ideas, fix bugs or even optimize the code. We truly appreciate each and every person that has contributed to the project and want to make it even more easier to do so by addressing some of the issues that have been brought up.</description></item><item><title>JMM is Now Shoko! Version 3.7 Beta</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 07:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over two months since the last blog post and the team has been hard at work on the next version, version 3.7. However as you can probably guess, besides continued development on the program, there have been quite a few other changes that have been made with the biggest being the new name.
Starting With Version 3.7, JMM Will Now be Known as Shoko. Over the past couple months, starting around mid-development of Version 3.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the JMM Server Web UI</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-the-jmm-server-webui/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 11:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-the-jmm-server-webui/</guid><description>One of the main goals for JMM is to make the programs and plugins as accessible to as many people as possible regardless of operating system. This has been a goal of the project for a very long time but has seen minimal progress, until today as we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce that we&amp;rsquo;re now one step closer to making this goal a reality.
We&amp;rsquo;d like to introduce everyone to out newest project, the JMM Server Web UI which you can see in the screenshot above.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.5.0.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-5-0-1-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 12:33:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-5-0-1-released/</guid><description>UPDATE: If JMM Server will not start for you please re-download version 3.5.0.1. The initial upload was missing a .dll file that has since been added.
After a very successful beta, JMM version 3.5.0.1 is available for download!
Before I go into the details of what&amp;rsquo;s new, we&amp;rsquo;d like to thank everyone that participated in the 3.5 beta. We received a lot of feedback that helped improve JMM with changes made and bugs discovered and fixed as a direct result.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.6.4 Brings a New Site</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-4-6-4-brings-a-new-site/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 10:44:55 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-4-6-4-brings-a-new-site/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
JMM has gone through a lot of changes over the past couple of months, both with JMM itself and as you might of noticed, the website as well. Before I go into detail about the new website and other changes lets talk about the new version of JMM!
With each release, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover a few of the new additions or changes but for a complete listing, check out the changelog.</description></item></channel></rss>