<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shoko on Plex on Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/shoko-on-plex/</link><description>Recent content in Shoko on Plex on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 01:06:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/shoko-on-plex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shoko Version 3.8.3 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-3-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 01:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-3-released/</guid><description>This release will be the last release for version 3.8 as we&amp;rsquo;re starting to work on some major internal changes that we&amp;rsquo;ve been planning for awhile. There are a couple features and issues we wanted to address for this release but we&amp;rsquo;re unable to, as such they will be included in the next major release which currently has no date.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.8.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-1-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 19:54:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-8-1-released/</guid><description>Almost a month later and we&amp;rsquo;re back with another update!
Version 3.8 was our biggest release to date and was released a very long time after Version 3.7. We&amp;rsquo;ve decided that going forward we&amp;rsquo;re going to aim for releasing updates at least once a month to ease migration for current users and reduce the amount of testing needed beforehand. We&amp;rsquo;ve also made some changes to our versioning system which we&amp;rsquo;ve outlined below.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7.0.4 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-4-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 03:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-4-released/</guid><description>We’ve released a maintenance update, version 3.7.0.4 for the following programs/plugins.
Shoko Server Shoko Desktop Shoko on Plex This maintenance update focuses on fixing various bugs that have been reported since we released 3.7.0.0. Assuming there are no new program breaking bugs, this will be the last maintenance release for this cycle. Also please be aware, while Shoko on Plex is listed as being updated, there is no new plugin to download as all of its changes were done in Shoko Server.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6 Brings Speed and Streaming</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-brings-speed-and-streaming/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 12:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-brings-speed-and-streaming/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
After a very successful beta that helped in identifying previously unknown issues and extended internal testing, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce that JMM Version 3.6.0.2 is available for download! Version 3.6 is by far the biggest update we&amp;rsquo;ve ever released containing over 40,000 lines of code added, changed and removed when compared to the previous version. While we generally try to limit the amount of new features added in the next version to reduce unforeseen issues, we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to hold back completed features and decided to do the extra work that was required to release this update.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.6 Beta Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-beta-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 07:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-6-beta-released/</guid><description>After completing our internal testing, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to release a public beta for the upcoming version 3.6!
If you take a look at the changelog you&amp;rsquo;ll see that a lot of work has gone into JMM version 3.6 with new features added, various improvements to existing features and functionality and fixing quite a few bugs. I&amp;rsquo;ve highlighted the two biggest changes and what the focus of this beta, however there are a lot of great additions with version 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.5.0.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-5-0-1-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 12:33:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-5-0-1-released/</guid><description>UPDATE: If JMM Server will not start for you please re-download version 3.5.0.1. The initial upload was missing a .dll file that has since been added.
After a very successful beta, JMM version 3.5.0.1 is available for download!
Before I go into the details of what&amp;rsquo;s new, we&amp;rsquo;d like to thank everyone that participated in the 3.5 beta. We received a lot of feedback that helped improve JMM with changes made and bugs discovered and fixed as a direct result.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.6.4 Brings a New Site</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-4-6-4-brings-a-new-site/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 10:44:55 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/version-3-4-6-4-brings-a-new-site/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
JMM has gone through a lot of changes over the past couple of months, both with JMM itself and as you might of noticed, the website as well. Before I go into detail about the new website and other changes lets talk about the new version of JMM!
With each release, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover a few of the new additions or changes but for a complete listing, check out the changelog.</description></item></channel></rss>