<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shokofin on Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/shokofin/</link><description>Recent content in Shokofin on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 09:16:46 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/shokofin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shoko Version 4.2.0 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-420-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 09:16:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-420-released/</guid><description>We are thrilled to announce the release of the latest version of Shoko! This new version introduces numerous enhancements, novel features, and bug fixes that improve the user experience significantly.
For a comprehensive list of changes, kindly visit our Changelog.
Basic ARM64 Support Thanks to Mohan226, we&amp;rsquo;re now able to offer an ARM64 build of Shoko on Linux
However, please note that all initial testing was conducted in a virtual machine.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 4.1.2 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-1-2-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 13:16:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-1-2-released/</guid><description>We are pleased to announce another maintenance release! In this release, we have fixed several reported bugs and issues that arose while working on the Jellyfin plugin, Shokofin, as well as made significant improvements to version 3 of our API.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.
Shoko Development We understand that our lack of frequent updates has been a source of concern, and we have been asked about it numerous times.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 4.1.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-1-1-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 15:20:53 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-4-1-1-released/</guid><description>This maintenance release addresses a few reported bugs and a few under-the-hood changes that won&amp;rsquo;t affect most users. However, its main purpose is it allows Shoko Server to work with our latest media player plugin, Shokofin. Read the announcement blog post about Shokofin if you&amp;rsquo;d like to learn more.
For a complete list of changes, check out the Changelog.
We also figured this blog post would be a good time to update everyone on the status of our in-development projects.</description></item><item><title>Hello Shokofin</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/hello-shokofin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/hello-shokofin/</guid><description>After being in development for quite some time, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce our Jellyfin plugin is now available to all users. We&amp;rsquo;ve previously talked about Shokofin before and with a starting version of 1.4.7, some of you might be wondering why it took so long for us to announce it.
Originally we had to wait for Jellyfin version 10.7 to be released, as we heavily relied on a change introduced in that version and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to make people install a dev version that could potentially cause damage to their database.</description></item><item><title>Shoko 2021 Project Update</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-2021-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 18:09:21 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-2021-roadmap/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret our team is working on multiple projects under the Shoko umbrella. Some of them we&amp;rsquo;ve talked about publicly, either on this website, on Discord, and on other platforms, and some we&amp;rsquo;ve only discussed internall amongst the team. So with it being a new year, we thought it would be best to outline the current status on all of our projects, as well as talk about some new ones in development.</description></item></channel></rss>