<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shoko Docs on Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/shoko-docs/</link><description>Recent content in Shoko Docs on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 02:34:25 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/shoko-docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shoko Docs Refresh</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-refresh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 02:34:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-refresh/</guid><description>After nearly five months, multiple designs and iterations, our new design for Shoko Docs is up! The main goal of this update was to make the design similar to the updated homepage as well as reevaluate the existing content as a lot of the information had become outdated or simply incorrect. To that end most of the content was rewritten and condensed to not only make it easier to follow, but create less confusion for future contributors.</description></item><item><title>Whats Next for Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/whats-next-for-shoko/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/whats-next-for-shoko/</guid><description>As mentioned earlier this week, we wanted to update the community on what we&amp;rsquo;ve got planned for Shoko and to give some clarification and possible updates on a few future projects &amp;amp; features that have been mentioned before on Discord. Its also important to note that not everything we discuss or bring up on Discord in regards to new features and improvements are actually planned for implementation. Sometimes its nothing more than just brainstorming and gauging reactions to said idea.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Docs Updated</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-updated/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 17:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-docs-updated/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been on our Discord server lately you&amp;rsquo;ve might of seen us asking for feedback on a new design we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on for Shoko Docs. With the feedback &amp;amp; suggestions we received from the community we&amp;rsquo;re happy to launch the latest version of Shoko Docs!
In the past to save time, we used a prebuilt template and customized it to our needs. While this worked in the beginning, we found that trying to add or modify the template outside of its designed purpose would cause issues.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Shoko Docs</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-shoko-docs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 19:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-shoko-docs/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re Back!
This past weekend we moved everything over to our ShokoAnime domain name making it our primary domain name and switched to a more reliable hosts. You may of noticed some changes around the site, during the downtime the site went through some intensive maintenance stripping away anything that was causing performance issues. We also decided to go for a less resource intensive theme that&amp;rsquo;s sleeker and for those of you visiting us on mobile, it looks great.</description></item></channel></rss>