<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web UI on Shoko</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/web-ui/</link><description>Recent content in Web UI on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shokoanime.com/blog/tag/web-ui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lets Talk Themes</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/lets-talk-themes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/lets-talk-themes/</guid><description>One of the oldest feature requests going all the way back to when the program was still called JMM, was the implementation of proper theme support for both Server and Desktop. Although it was explored, limitations related to WPF made this request near impossible and a huge time sink for the devs.
With the announcement of Shoko Desktop 2, its change from a C# program to a web application and the eventual decision to merge Shoko Desktop features into the Server Web UI.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7.0.1 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-1-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 20:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-0-1-released/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve released a maintenance update, version 3.7.01 for the following programs/plugins.
Shoko Server Shoko Desktop My Anime 3 This maintenance update should resolve all migration issues, JMM uninstall issues and also includes some additional bug fixes. For a full list of changes please check the changelog. If you are still encountering any migration issues on 3.7.0.1, please contact us on Discord.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Version 3.7 Released</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/shoko-version-3-7-released/</guid><description>Hello Everyone,
While originally scheduled for earlier this month, Shoko Version 3.7 is finally available for download!
Version 3.7 is a big milestone for us for a variety of reasons that all share the same goal, to make Shoko even better for both users and developers. Shoko is open-source for a reason, we want people to contribute, to implement new ideas, fix bugs or even optimize the code. We truly appreciate each and every person that has contributed to the project and want to make it even more easier to do so by addressing some of the issues that have been brought up.</description></item><item><title>JMM is Now Shoko! Version 3.7 Beta</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 07:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/jmm-is-now-shoko-version-3-7-beta/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over two months since the last blog post and the team has been hard at work on the next version, version 3.7. However as you can probably guess, besides continued development on the program, there have been quite a few other changes that have been made with the biggest being the new name.
Starting With Version 3.7, JMM Will Now be Known as Shoko. Over the past couple months, starting around mid-development of Version 3.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the JMM Server Web UI</title><link>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-the-jmm-server-webui/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 11:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shokoanime.com/blog/introducing-the-jmm-server-webui/</guid><description>One of the main goals for JMM is to make the programs and plugins as accessible to as many people as possible regardless of operating system. This has been a goal of the project for a very long time but has seen minimal progress, until today as we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce that we&amp;rsquo;re now one step closer to making this goal a reality.
We&amp;rsquo;d like to introduce everyone to out newest project, the JMM Server Web UI which you can see in the screenshot above.</description></item></channel></rss>